#### Contact

celeste.ratajczak.rn.msn@gm ail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/celesteratajczak-msn-rn-ba-org-mgmta1495148 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Telemetry
Cardiac Care
Acute Care

### Languages

English

# Celeste Ratajczak, MSN, RN, BA Org. Mgmt

Progressive Care/ Critical Care Unit RN at Southern CA Hospital United States

## Summary

Nursing professional actively working in Acute and Critical Care units at area hospitals; Experience in care of medically complex adult and pediatric patients in Ambulatory Surgery, Pre- and Post Cath Lab, Med/ Surg, Telemetry, and Progressive Care units.

American Association of Critical- Care Nurses (AACN) Chapter Ambassador.

Former Board Member, San Diego Chapter AACN.

# Experience

Southern CA Hospital
Progressive Care/ Critical Care Unit RN
2016 - Present (4 years)
Southern CA

Critical Care Nursing, Post Cath Lab

Travel RN, Progressive Care/ Telemetry/ Definitive Observation Travel RN

Staffing Agency, area hospitals RN, Telemetry, Med- Surg 2013 - Present (7 years) Greater San Diego Area, Orange County

Accountable nursing care for Telemetry Unit and Med- Surg assigned patients. Responds quickly and accurately to changes in patient condition and/or response to treatment. Communicates with physician about changes in the patient's clinical condition. Conducts cardiac monitoring, analyzes results of diagnostic studies and monitors patients. Performs nursing interventions and responds accordingly. Displays critical thinking skills for intervening with appropriate interventions for emergent care, including critical care IV drips.

SDAACN
AACN Ambassador
2015 - Present (5 years)
American Association of Critical-Care Nurses (AACN)

Recruit new and lapsed members for AACN.

Provide information and encouragement to RNs seeking advanced certification in Progressive Care (PCCN) and other specialties.

Ambulatory (Outpatient) Surgery Center Post -Op RN, Ambulatory Surgery 2012 - 2013 (1 year)

Directly responsible for postoperative nursing care of the patient in the ambulatory care setting. Incorporates a sense of wellness by allowing the patient's family to be reunited with patient as soon as feasible. Encourages patient self-care through patient teaching and education. Provides leadership in the clinical and managerial operations of the organization. Interprets facility policy and procedures, engaged in active involvement with Quality Assurance and the Core Leadership Team.

Magnet Hospital Imaging Assistant 2011 - 2012 (1 year)

Assure patient stability with proper transport technique. Safely transfer and transport patients from hospital rooms to assigned imaging department modalities such as CT scan, Interventional Radiology, Nuclear Medicine, and X Ray. Communicate with different departments, function as a team player.

Commercial and RE Brokerage Senior Commercial Loan Officer, Realtor 2001 - 2011 (10 years) San Diego, CA

KSWB- TV (Tribune Co.) Marketing Consultant 1997 - 2001 (4 years)

## Education

United States University

MSN (Master of Science, Nursing), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Page 2 of 3

Ashford University
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Organizational Management